(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-13T22:11:18.610028",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
新衣装お披露目＆超告知あり！？
New Outfit Reveal & Super Announcement!?
Sakura Miko Birthday Live 2026 Fashion Beat
さくらみこ
Sakura Miko
大空スバル　常闇トワ
Oozora Subaru, Tokoyami Towa
白上フブキ　大神ミオ
Shirakami Fubuki, Ookami Mio
百鬼あやめ　戌神ころね　宝鐘マリン
Nakiri Ayame, Inugami Korone, Houshou Marine
ファッションビート
Fashion Beat
Nya! Hello!!
The beautiful days!!
割目しちゃってくれ！
Keep your eyes peeled!
Please call 『Elite』!!
(Funky dancin baby! ah)
さぁ、待ったなしだ！始めちゃえ！
Now, there's no waiting! Let's get started!
今日も気ぃ引き締めえーて えいや！で挑戦だ
Today too, brace yourself and challenge with a shout!
躊躇は厳禁 足踏みしないで
Hesitation is strictly forbidden, don't stand still!
一緒に「せぇの！」でもっと前に進もうね？
Together, on "one, two!" let's move further forward, okay?
さぁ、なんとかしちゃえ！飛び込んで
Now, somehow it'll work out! Dive in!
なんたってジッとしたっててても人生は冒険だ
After all, even if you stay still, life is an adventure!
こんがらがったら またわかんないぞ
If it gets tangled, you won't understand again!
道のりは困難だ！なんなんだ！上等だ！ダンダンダン！あはっ
The path is difficult! What of it! Bring it on! Dan-dan-dan! Ahah!
メソメソしちゃって 気持ちに「待った」しちゃって
Moping around, putting a "wait" on your feelings...
あれ？一体全体どうしたん？
Huh? What on earth happened?
絶対絶命？
Is this a desperate situation?
君たちには
For all of you...
涙は似合わないね！
...tears don't suit you!
大大大大大冒険に飛び出そうぜ！良いじゃんねぇ！
Let's dive into a great, great, great adventure! Isn't that great!
大大大大大失敗も重ねて成長して
Overcoming great, great, great failures to grow...
happyなfeel soで 君と笑い話にしよう
With a happy feel so, let's turn it into a joke with you!
大大大大大問題も吹き飛ばせ！いつか
Blow away even great, great, great problems! Someday...
大大大大大団円の素敵な結末へ
...to a wonderful happy ending of a grand finale!
please me!! さぁ、付いてきて？
Please me!! Now, come along with me?
進め！前代未聞のnew world!
Forward! Into an unprecedented new world!
あながち間違ってる ま～た墓穴も掘ってる
It's not entirely wrong, digging my own grave again!
勉強！勉強！ (はいはいはい、知ってます。待って、なんか違ってる！)
Study! Study! (Yes, yes, yes, I know. Wait, something's wrong!)
ぶっちゃけ有識者の皆様に感謝してます！
To be honest, I'm grateful to all the experts!
nice comment's 待ってんぜ (あ～ね)
I'm waiting for your nice comments (Ah, I see)
ウジウジしちゃって 心にロックしちゃって
Fretting and putting a lock on your heart...
ほら、だんだんだんだんダウンしちゃ
See, you're gradually, gradually getting down...
絶対絶命！？
A desperate situation!?
君たちには
For all of you...
笑顔が足りてないね！
...you're lacking smiles!
大大大大大好きじゃ済まさない！良いじゃんねぇ！
I won't let it end with just "I love you so, so, so much"! Isn't that great!
大大大大大満足のその上の感動をもっと欲しがっちゃって？
Wanting even more of the emotion beyond great satisfaction?
豪快に贅沢に行こう
Let's go dynamically and luxuriously!
全然前進しないなって凹んじゃったって
Even if you get depressed thinking you're not moving forward at all...
ならば全身全霊 エンジン全開 本気(マジ)の全力で
...then with all your heart and soul, engine at full blast, with serious full power!
Nya! Hello!! さぁbeautifulに！
Nya! Hello!! Now, beautifully!
意気込んで 進め！freedom way!
With high spirits, move forward! Freedom way!
(wow wow) 乗り遅れんなよ皆さん！ (wow wow)
(wow wow) Don't miss the ride, everyone! (wow wow)
声を聞かせてくれ！yeah! (wow wow)
Let me hear your voice! Yeah! (wow wow)
歌おう 声高らかに (wow wow)
Let's sing, loud and clear! (wow wow)
ベイベー ベイベー なんていうか…
Baby, baby, how should I put it...
あぁ、なんだかちょっと言い表せない
Ah, somehow I can't quite express it.
一人ぼっちで見てた光景を
The scenery I used to look at all by myself...
今はきっとあなたと冒険してる！
...now I'm surely adventuring with you!
大大大大大大大大大大大大大大好きじゃ収まらない！
Just saying "I love you" sixteen times isn't enough to contain it!
だから最大最高レベルにガチの全力で！
So with serious full power at the maximum, highest level!
Nya! Hello!! 届けちゃうぜ！
Nya! Hello!! I'm gonna deliver it!
ずっと大冒険しよう yeah!!
Let's go on a great adventure forever, yeah!!
大大大問題も吹き飛ばせ！いつか
Blow away even great, great, great problems! Someday...
大大大大大団円の素敵な結末へ
...to a wonderful happy ending of a grand finale!
please me!! さぁ、付いてきて？
Please me!! Now, come along with me?
進め！前代未聞のnew world!
Forward! Into an unprecedented new world!
割目しちゃってくれ！
Keep your eyes peeled!
Please call 『Elite』!!
「とくべちゅ、して？」
"Do something special... for me?"
「I love you」じゃ足りない
"I love you" is not enough,
一番 大事がいい
I want to be your number one.
君が作るオリジナルの
An original made by you...
特別 チューして
Give me a special kiss.
眩しくって目が覚めて
I wake up to a dazzling brightness,
愛おしく思ってよ
so please love me dearly.
眠り姫のように
Just like Sleeping Beauty,
優しく口づけて
give me a gentle kiss.
ゴミめいたこの世界
In this world that feels like trash,
ピュアがかる君がいる
there you are, filled with purity.
全てに触れずに
Without touching anything else,
2人だけでいよう
let's just be the two of us.
私のこと独占して
Monopolize me entirely,
君だけのモノになってもいい
I don't mind becoming yours alone.
なんでもある日の「なんでもない」
Notice the ordinary details
気付いてね
of these uneventful days.
Oh baby 「I love you」じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" isn't enough,
君の「特別」にして
make me your "special one."
ねえもっと Give me a kiss
Hey, give me more kisses,
もう私は君でいっぱいよ
I'm already completely filled with you.
ほどけないリボン結び
A ribbon tied so tightly it won't come undone,
小指キュッて縛って
bind our pinkies together tight.
そうよ一生一緒がいいもん
Yes, I want us to be together forever,
とくべチュが欲しい
I want your special kiss.
2人きり週末は
When we're all alone on the weekend,
奏でてよハーモニー
let's play a harmony.
流れ星見たら
If you see a shooting star,
私を想ってほしい
I want you to think of me.
あまあまな君なのに
Even though you're so sweet to me,
広い街吸い込まれ
you get swallowed up by the wide city.
戦う姿に
Seeing you working so hard,
大きいなはなまるだね
earns a big gold star from me.
好きなところ、優しいとこ。
The things I like, your gentle side.
嫌いなとこも、優しいとこ。
Even the things I dislike, your gentle side.
誰にもあげない 私だけ
I won't give you to anyone, I'm keeping you...
独り占め！
...all to myself!
う〜だって 今までの人と同じはいらないんです
Because I don't want the same things as before.
ねえもっと Give me more love
Hey, give me more love,
私のために生きてほしいんです
I want you to live just for me.
だからウサギと私は
That's why bunnies and I...
寂しくさせないで
...don't let us get lonely.
そんなんじゃ束縛じゃないわ
That's not enough to be called binding,
苦しいのが好き
I love the sweet pain of it.
ショートケーキ
Just like a strawberry...
イチゴみたいに座ってもいい？
...sitting on top of a shortcake, can I sit there?
赤く甘い恋だもん
After all, it's a red, sweet love.
誰かにあげた「大好き」も
Take back the "I love yous" you gave others,
返してもらって
get them returned,
全部私に ちょうだい、もっと！
and give them all to me, even more!
君は神様が作る
You are a miracle-like person
奇跡のようなヒト
created by God.
拗ねた顔も その寝顔も
Whether your pouting face or sleeping face,
守ってあげるね
I'll protect them all.
Oh baby 「I love you」じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" isn't enough,
君の「特別」にして
make me your "special one."
ねえもっと Give me a kiss
Hey, give me more kisses,
もう私は君でいっぱいよ
I'm already completely filled with you.
ほどけないリボン結び
A ribbon tied so tightly it won't come undone,
小指キュッて縛って
bind our pinkies together tight.
ねえ baby 最初で最後の
Hey baby, make it our first and last...
とくべチュにしてね
...special kiss.
はーい、みんなにゃっはろー！
Hi everyone, nyahallo!
エリート巫女アイドルのさくらみこー！
I'm elite shrine maiden idol, Sakura Miko!
さくらみこ生誕祭2026 ファッションビートに来てくれてどうもありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to the Sakura Miko Birthday Live 2026 "Fashion Beat"!
今年でなんと、みこちゃん、18.8歳になりました！
This year, Mikochi actually turned 18.8 years old!
多分18.8歳だよね？
I think it's 18.8 years old, right?
あの、0.1で刻んでいく系のVTuberですから。
Well, I'm the type of VTuber who ages by 0.1 years at a time.
今年も18.8歳になっております！うわー！
So this year, I have successfully become 18.8 years old! Whoa!
そしてそして、今回のライブのテーマは、ファッションビートにちなんでですね、
And, of course, the theme of this live show, in line with "Fashion Beat"...
ファッションとなっております！
...is "fashion"!
いろんなね、演出が盛りだくさんなので、ぜひ楽しんでください！
There are lots of different performances, so please enjoy them!
じゃあね、ちょっともうファッションにちなんで、みこちゃんもちょっとだけチェンジしちゃおうかなー？
Now then, speaking of fashion, should Mikochi change her outfit just a little bit too?
はい、上向いててください。
Okay, please look up.
よいしょ。
Up we go.
はい、じゃーん！
Okay, ta-da!
ということで、クリスマスのね、ライブではね、あの、あまり...
So, for this Christmas live show, actually...
こちらの
This is...
えー、キャストオフバージョンになっております！
...the cast-off version!
こんな感じになってます、可愛いでしょ？
It looks like this. Cute, right?
ちょっとセクシーですけどね
Though it's a little sexy.
はい
Yes.
はーい
Alright!
はい！
Yes!
はい、次の曲はこれで披露しようと思っております！
I'm planning to perform the next song in this!
そして、先ほどね、二曲ね、お送りしましたがどうでしたか？
And I just performed two songs earlier. How was it?
みこのオリ曲の「ダイダイダイファンタジスタ」と
Miko's original song, "Dai Dai Dai Fantasista"...
そして、みこの大好きなアイドルさんの、いとっぱさんの特別仕様としては
and as a special version of a song by my favorite idol, Itoppa-san...
披露させていただきました！
...I got to perform it!
とっても可愛かったでしょ？
It was super cute, right?
きゅるん、きゅるん
Kyurun, kyurun!
はい！
Yes!
あ、そうだ！ステージもね、ちょっと見せたいんですけど...
Oh, that's right! I also want to show you the stage...
見てください！
Look at this!
こちら！今回のテーマにちなんで作っていただきました！
This was made based on this stream's theme!
ドレッサーとかね
Like a dresser!
メチャクチャね、なんかこう、みこが小人になったみたいなんですけど
It's so huge, it makes me feel like a dwarf!
ね、とっても可愛くなっております！
Right? It turned out super cute!
そしてこちらのね、トルソーに、みこちゃんの歴代の衣装とかも少し飾ってあります！
On these torsos, some of Miko's past outfits are on display!
全部じゃないんですけどね！
Though not all of them!
はい！
Yes!
えー、そして、えー、最後にですね、たくさんの告知があったりとか...
And lastly, there will be lots of announcements...
新衣装のお披露目はございますので！
and a new outfit reveal!
ぜひ、楽しんでもらえたらなと思っております！
So I hope you'll look forward to it and enjoy!
では！
Now then!
早速ゲストパート、行こうと思いますよ！
Let's get right into the guest segment!
よいしょっと
Up we go.
それでは、このあとも楽しんでね！
Please enjoy the rest of the show!
よし！
Alright!
ファッションモンスター
Fashion Monster
おもしろいって言いたいのに
You wanna say it's fun
いえないなんてつまらないでしょ
but can't, how silly is that
おなじになっていい子でなんて
Don't wanna be a good kid like the rest
いたくないってキミもそうでしょ
bet you also don't want that
だれかのルールに
I don't wanna be tied down
しばられたくはないの
by other people's rules
わがまま ドキドキ
So selfish, heart pounding
このままでいたい
I wanna stay the way I am
ファッションモンスター
Fashion Monster
このせまいこころの檻も
I wanna break apart the confining
こわして自由になりたいの
cage of my heart and be free
ファッションモンスター
Fashion Monster
感覚をとぎすませてキミのように
Let me hone my senses, just like you are
すいこまれてく螺旋模様みたいに
Being swallowed up, pulled into a spiral,
I wanna be free
ファッションモンスター
Fashion Monster
ただふつうに生きたいのに
Just wanna live my life
へんなことってつまらないでしょ
but they say I'm odd, how silly is that
きめつけないでいい子でなんて
Don't judge me, I don't wanna be a good kid,
いたくないってキミもそうでしょ
bet you also don't want that
だれかの
Other people's...
ルールに
by rules...
しばられたくはないの
I don't want to be bound.
わがまま
Selfish,
ドキドキ
my heart pounding,
このままでいたい
I want to stay the way I am.
ファッションモンスター
Fashion Monster
鉄の首飾りをはずして
Take off the iron necklace
ただ自由にいきたいだけ
and just live freely.
ファッションモンスター
Fashion Monster
このせまいこころの檻も
This narrow cage of my heart,
こわして自由になりたいの
I want to break it and be free.
ファッションモンスター
Fashion Monster
咲き誇れ花よ舞い踊れ
Bloom in full glory, flowers, dance around!
明日を虹色に染め上げて
Dye tomorrow in rainbow colors!
いくぞー！
Let's go!
夢色フェスティバル
[Title: Yumeiro Festival]
そいや！そいや！
Soiya! Soiya!
はーどっこい！
Haa-dokkoi!
はっじまるぞー！
Here we go!
今から歌うはウルトラスーパー
The song we'll sing now is ultra-super,
いといとおかしの夢色リズム
extremely charming, a dream-colored rhythm!
おかしなゆえにね 心惹かれるの
Because it's strange, it captivates my heart.
ま、そんな話はどうでもいい！
Well, that kind of talk doesn't matter anyway!
大事なるのは楽しむ心
What's important is an enjoying heart!
準備はいくな？ 遅れないてよね
Are you ready? Don't fall behind!
あ！
Ah!
準備万端！ 呼吸を乱して
Fully prepared! Get out of breath,
靴紐結んで
tie your shoelaces,
３・２・１で飛び出して！
and jump out on 3, 2, 1!
ワクワクしたいの！
I want to feel excited!
ドキドキしたくない？
Don't you want your heart to pound?
ウキウキさせてよ！
Make me cheerful!
もういい？
Are we good yet?
いやいやまだまだ！
No, no, not yet!
なんていうか止まらない！
I mean, we can't stop!
まだまだ明日の景色を見ていたくない？
Don't you want to keep seeing tomorrow's scenery?
それ！よいしょ！はい！
Sore! Yoisho! Yes!
咲き誇れ！
Bloom in full glory!
だから２人は最高のフェスティバル
That's why we're the best festival!
お祭りリズムでノリノリ
Grooving to the festival rhythm,
笑顔満開無限大
smiles blooming infinitely!
It's alright!
舞い踊れ！
Dance around!
君色教えて
Tell me your color,
気になっちゃうから
because I'm curious!
そんな感じで夢のビート聴かせてよ
Just like that, let me hear the dream beat!
そいや！そいや！
Soiya! Soiya!
はーどっこい！
Haa-dokkoi!
どっこいしょー！
Dokkoisho!
続けて歌うはウルトラスーパー
Continuing on, we'll sing ultra-super,
いといとおかしの夢色リズム
extremely charming, a dream-colored rhythm!
もしかしましても さっきも言ったっけ？
Could it be we already said this earlier?
ま、そんな話は どうでもいい！
Well, that kind of talk doesn't matter anyway!
大事なるのは信じる心
What's important is a believing heart!
キミだけに聴こえる リズムに任せて
Leave it to the rhythm only you can hear!
あ！
Ah!
星空きらめく街を
The city sparkling under the starry sky,
もっともっと照らすから
we'll light it up more and more!
３・２・１で扉開けて！
Open the door on 3, 2, 1!
ワクワクしたいの！
I want to feel excited!
ドキドキしたくない？
Don't you want your heart to pound?
ウキウキさせてよ！
Make me cheerful!
もういい？
Are we good yet?
いやいやまだまだ！
No, no, not yet!
なんていうか終わらない！
I mean, it won't end!
なんていうか止まらない！
I mean, we can't stop!
今宵も君と夢色を抱きしめて
Tonight again, embrace the dream colors with you,
いっくぞー！
Let's go!
咲き誇れ！
Bloom in full glory!
だから２人は最高のフェスティバル
That's why we're the best festival!
曖昧なリズムにドキドキさ
Our hearts pound to the vague rhythm!
空に満開無限大
Blooming infinitely in the sky!
It's alright!
舞い上がれ！
Soar high!
君色教えて 内緒にするから
Tell me your color, I'll keep it a secret!
そんな感じで
Just like that,
夢のビートきざもうよ
Let's carve out the beat of our dreams!
さわげー！
Let's make some noise!
咲き誇れ
Bloom proudly!
だから最高のフェスティバル
That's why this is the best festival!
祭り囃子リズムでノリノリ
Grooving to the festival music beat!
笑顔満開無限大
Full of smiles, infinitely,
It's Alright!
舞い踊れ
Dance away,
編み上げて
braid it up,
君色教えて
Tell me your color,
気になっちゃう color
I'm curious about your color!
そんな感じで
Just like that,
夢のビート聴かせてよ
let me hear the beat of your dreams!
だから止まれない！
So, we can't stop!
はっ！
Ha!
ソイヤ！ソイヤ！
Soiya! Soiya!
はーどっこい！
Ha-dokkoi!
どっこいしょ！どっこいしょ！
Dokkoisho! Dokkoisho!
ぶつけたところから
From the place where we collided,
熟れていく
ripening...
果実のように
...just like a fruit.
僕らは些細なことで
Over the smallest things,
へこたれたよな
we would feel so discouraged, wouldn't we?
かさぶたになれずに
Unable to even form a scab,
息せき切って
Out of breath,
がむしゃらに
and running recklessly,
輝く一等星をめがけて
aiming for that shining first-magnitude star,
手を伸ばしたよな
we reached our hands out, didn't we?
繊細されど大胆だ
Delicate, yet we are bold!
うるさい これが切り札だ
Shut up, this is our trump card!
泣き虫されど熱血だ
Crybabies, yet we are hot-blooded!
うるさい これが持ち味だ
Shut up, this is our defining trait!
未開拓冒険地帯
An unexplored adventure zone,
好奇心旺盛時代
an era overflowing with curiosity!
何が綺麗かは分かる
We know what beauty is,
見る目ならばある
we certainly have an eye for it!
恥ずかしいか青春は
Is youth something to be embarrassed of?
馬鹿らしいか真剣は
Is being serious something foolish?
僕ら全力でやってんだ
We are giving it everything we've got!
振りかざせ存在を
Brandish your very existence,
掻き乱せ心臓を
stir up your heart!
あとどれくらい続いていくだろう
How much longer will this keep going on?
守り抜いた青春が
The youth we protected to the end
何よりも贅沢だ きっと
is the greatest luxury of all, surely.
いつか
Someday,
焦がれ思い返す
we'll yearn and look back on it.
名前のない関係を
These nameless relationships,
捨てきれない感情を
these feelings we can't throw away...
何気ない今日を忘れないでね
Please never forget this casual today.
悩んでた種の色が
The color of the seed we worried over...
昨日とはまるで違うとか
is completely different from yesterday.
そんなの日常茶飯事だね
That kind of thing is just an everyday occurrence,
心は素直のようだ
it seems our hearts are honest after all.
戦友だとか親友は
Whether we call them brothers-in-arms or best friends,
うるさい どれも正解だ
shut up, either one is correct!
初恋だとか失恋は
Whether it's first love or heartbreak,
うるさい どれも宝石だ
shut up, each of them is a gem!
天才的人生計画
A genius life plan,
問題集対抗美学
exams and rebellious aesthetics.
君はなにしてんのかな
I wonder what you are doing right now,
話がしたい
I want to talk to you.
風に乗って青春が
Riding on the wind, our youth
この想いを運んだ
carried these feelings over.
僕ら全力を超えたいんだ
We want to go beyond our absolute best!
立ちすくむ同志だって
Even our friends who stand frozen,
引き連れていこうぜ
let's take them along with us.
この上ない今日を
This day that couldn't be any better,
過ごしていたいよ
I want to spend it with you.
今しかできない事がある
There are things we can only do right now,
今しかできない恋がある
there is a love we can only experience right now.
今しかできないから僕らに
Because it's only right now,
託された時間が惜しい
the time we've been given is so precious.
今しか見られない君の笑顔も
Your smile that I can only see right now,
君の涙も
your tears, too,
君の全てでも
even everything about you,
大人びていく
is starting to grow up.
有限だから最高だ
Because it is limited, it is the best!
恥ずかしいか青春は
Is youth embarrassing?
馬鹿らしいか真剣は
Is being serious foolish?
僕ら全力でやってんだ
We are giving it everything we've got!
振りかざせ存在を
Brandish your existence!
掻き乱せ心臓を
Stir up your heart!
胸に刻めば続いていくだろう
If you engrave it in your chest, it will go on.
守り抜いた青春が
The youth we protected to the end
何よりも贅沢だ
is the greatest luxury of all.
きっといつか
Surely, someday,
焦がれ思い返す
we will look back on it with yearning.
名前のない関係を
A relationship without a name,
捨てきれない感情を
and these feelings we can't throw away,
何気ない今日を忘れないでね
please don't forget this ordinary today.
この上ない今日を忘れないでね
Please don't forget this incomparable today.
アイ、アイドルだから
B-Because I'm an idol,
挑み続けるんだ 君と夢見るんだ
I'll keep on fighting, dreaming with you.
不器用で悪いか
Is it wrong to be clumsy?
咲き誇るよ
I will bloom proudly!
初のイベント
My first event,
需要無しデフォ
defaulted with no demand.
そんな私が夢を見ました
Even so, I dared to dream
アイドルという生き方
of living life as an idol,
憧れて
with longing in my heart.
「無敵エリート」
"Invincible elite!"
「笑顔はチート」
"My smile is a cheat code!"
こんな私を見てくれる君
You, who look at someone like me—
好きなとこはどこですか？
what is it that you like about me?
わがままを
Please forgive
許して
my selfishness.
ステージ経験値 涙滲んで
My stage experience is blurred by tears,
それでも絶対負けたくないくらい
but even so, I don't want to lose at all.
桜にメッセージ乗せて届け
Send my message riding on the cherry blossoms,
愛で溢れますように
so it can overflow with love!
アイ、アイドルだから
B-Because I'm an idol,
挑み続けるんだ 君と夢見るんだ
I'll keep on fighting, dreaming with you.
不器用で悪いか
Is it wrong to be clumsy?
咲き誇れ
Bloom proudly!
妄想だけじゃ終わらせない
I won't let this end as just a fantasy.
私らしく
In my own way,
桜色ね
dyed in cherry blossom pink!
磨いたスキル
My polished skills,
実力発揮
showing my true ability.
楽しめる日も増えてきたんだ
The days I can enjoy have been increasing.
アイドルとして生きてる
I am living my life as an idol,
君のおかげ
all thanks to you!
アホ毛はキュート！ 勝ち確ルート！
My cowlick is cute! A guaranteed victory route!
そんな私についてきてよね！
Make sure to keep on following me!
ドジなとこも許されて
Even my clumsy side is forgiven—
最強じゃん！
isn't that just the best?
痛いの言いたいのグッと飲み込んで
Swallowing down the pain and complaints,
笑顔で笑顔増やしたいな
I want to spread smiles with my own smile!
桜前線が君の町に
Just like the cherry blossom front reaching your town,
春を届けるように
delivering the warmth of spring!
アイ、アイドルだけは
The one thing, being an idol,
譲りたくないんだ 君に見せたいんだ
is something I won't give up! I want to show you!
理想越え挑むよ
Going beyond my ideals, I'll challenge myself.
駆け抜けろ
Run right through!
最高景色見せてあげる
I'll show you the most beautiful view.
信じていいよ
You can believe in me,
桜を
and in the cherry blossoms!
さぁ
Now,
皆で咲かそう
let's bloom together!
満開のピンクで
With cherry blossoms in full bloom,
世界染めて
let's paint the world pink!
あぁ
Ah,
この涙はね
these tears, you see...
あぁ この涙はね
Ah, these tears...
悲しい方じゃないから
aren't from sadness...
安心して
so please don't worry.
きれいだね
It's beautiful, isn't it?
今年も誕生日お祝いしてくれてありがとう！
Thank you for celebrating my birthday this year too!
みんな、大好きだよー！
I love you all!
あ、アイドルだから
Because, because I'm an idol...
挑み続けるんだ
I will keep on challenging.
君と夢見るんだ
I will dream with you.
不器用で悪いか
Is being clumsy so bad?
咲き誇れ
Bloom proudly!
妄想だけじゃ終わらせない
I won't let things end with just delusions.
私らしく
In my own way...
桜色ね
...in cherry blossom color, right?
みんなー！ありがとうー！
Everyone! Thank you!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
ありがとね！
はい！ありがとうー！
Yes! Thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ちゅっ！ありがとう！
Blows kiss! Thank you!
お祝いしてくれてありがとね！
Thank you for celebrating!
楽しんでるー？
Are you enjoying yourselves?
ありがとう！
Thank you!
うー、まっ！
Mwah!
見てるよー！みんな見てるよー！
I see you! I see all of you!
よしっ！
Alright!
ということで！ライブ、まだまだ盛り上がる準備できてますかー！
And with that! Are you ready to get even more hyped for the live show?!
みんな！まだまだ見逃さないでね！
Everyone! Don't miss a thing yet!
よし、次の曲行きます！
Alright, let's go to the next song!
Now I'm ready, I'm ready to go
花が咲く時が来たんだ
The time for the flower to bloom has come
Are you ready? わかるでしょ
Are you ready? You know it, right?
やってみせる Make it through
I'll show you I can make it through
ほら ほら ほら ソワソワしだした
Look, look, look, you're starting to get restless
時は過ぎちゃうから 今すぐ すぐに
Because time slips away, right now, immediately
Let's work it out
もう 目を背けやしないんだ
I won't look away anymore
自分で M@KE IT BETTER
I'll make it better myself
作る正解を
to create the right answer
I just wanna, just wanna find somebody
私よりも強気なドクター
who is bolder than me, Doctor
Make you hot, make you hot
準備体操お済みですか？
Are you finished with your warm-up exercises?
Victory
So let's now start the war!
I'm fighting my way
夢の二乗
The square of my dreams
信じて進むだけ
I'll just believe and move forward
誰にも絶対 負ける気なんか無い
There is no way I'll lose to anyone
君に見せたいの 彼方の景色を
I want to show you the scenery beyond
恋に焦がれ 情熱全て
Yearning with love, with all my passion
もっと先を知りたい
I want to know what lies further ahead
もう止まらない
I can't stop anymore
I will lead the way, follow my way
Hey!
Don't kill my vibe
行こう 一番上まで
Let's go to the very top!
ちょっと待ってなんか不快なノイズ
Wait a minute, some unpleasant noise...
限界など蹴っ飛ばしちゃうね
I'll kick away any limits!
蹴散らすため戦うわけではないの
I'm not fighting to scatter them away
Just wanna keep challenging myself
こんなファンタジー
A fantasy like this...
ハマったらもっともっと欲しくなっちゃうよ
once you're hooked, you'll want more and more!
もう 何も 恐れはしないんだ
I won't fear anything anymore
君となら勇気がするから
Because with you, I feel courageous
Come join us
ほら 今聞こえて来るから
Look, because I can hear it now...
私を呼ぶ声
...the voice calling my name
I'm fighting with myself
負けなんてない
There is no defeat
勝負受けて立つだけ
I'll just accept the challenge
もう自分以外 私に勝てない
No one but myself can beat me
君がいれば何度も立ち上がるわ
If you are here, I will rise up again and again!
雨を受け 夜を抜け
Enduring the rain, passing through the night
青空の光 求めた
I sought the light of the blue sky
Whoa
一つも無駄は無いさ
Not a single thing is a waste
パワーに変えて 輝いていくから
I'll turn it into power and shine!
KIRA KIRA 弾けた
Sparkling, it burst!
Ah 神の思し召しだ
Ah, it is God's will!
連れてってあげるよ Make you high
I'll take you with me, make you high
後悔はさせない
I won't let you regret it
超えるんだ
We will surpass it!
Victory
So let's now start the war!
I'm fighting with myself
負けなんてない
There is no defeat
勝負受けて立つだけ
I'll just accept the challenge
もう自分以外 私に勝てない
No one but myself can beat me
君がいれば何度も立ち上がるわ
If you are here, I will rise up again and again!
愛を歌え 想い全て
Sing of love, all your thoughts...
逃げたくはない 待てない
I don't want to run away, I can't wait
まだ終われない
It's not over yet
I need you to stay
You make me feel okay
Hey!
It's time to shine
行こう 空の上まで
Let's go up into the sky
Weh oh weh oh
Ram pam pam para pum pum pa
Ahhh ooh uh
唸るぜ
I'm roaring!
血泥ついたって
Even if covered in blood and mud,
守りたい
I want to protect you.
革命道中だって
Even in the middle of a revolution,
君に夢中
I'm crazy about you.
暗闇染み込む世界で見つけた
I found you in a world steeped in darkness.
センチメンタルな恋
A sentimental love.
甘くぬかるんだ眼差し
A sweet, muddy look in your eyes,
変に色気あるから困った
I'm troubled because you're strangely alluring.
手をつなぐ勇気出したくて
Wanting to summon the courage to hold hands,
身の程わきまえててできないね
knowing my place, I just can't do it.
暗いトンネルの壁 したたり落ちる悲鳴
The dark tunnel walls, dripping with screams.
しめやかに高鳴る心
My heart solemnly throbbing.
ダメダメ 待て待て
No, no, wait, wait.
呪いも病も抱きしめたい
I want to embrace even the curses and illness.
ここらで暴れちゃっていいかな
Is it okay if I run wild right about here?
あぁ 唸るぜ
Ah, I'll roar!
血泥ついたって
Even if covered in blood and mud,
守りたい
I want to protect you.
革命道中だって
Even in the middle of a revolution,
君に夢中
I'm crazy about you.
暗闇染み込む世界で見つけた
I found you in a world steeped in darkness.
センチメンタルな恋
A sentimental love.
ダメダメ 待て待て
No, no, wait, wait.
なりふり構わず側にいたい
I want to be by your side, no matter how I look.
不器用な君にも期待しちゃうよ
I find myself expecting things from clumsy you, too.
しがみつけば消えそうな君に
To you, who seem like you'll disappear if I cling to you,
恋の爪立てて近づいてもいい？
is it okay if I dig in the claws of love and get closer?
身を任せて抱かれて全て失ってもいい
Surrendering myself to your embrace, I don't care if I lose everything.
しめやかに高鳴る心
My heart solemnly throbbing.
ダメダメ 待て待て
No, no, wait, wait.
呪いも病も君となら
Even curses and sickness, if it's with you,
ここらで暴れちゃっていいかな
is it okay if I run wild right about here?
あぁ 泣けるぜ
Ah, I could cry!
絶句しちゃうまで
Until I'm left speechless,
離れない
I won't let go.
革命道中だって
Even in the middle of a revolution,
君に夢中
I'm crazy about you.
揺蕩う旅の狭間で見つけた
I found you in the midst of a drifting journey.
センチメンタルな恋
A sentimental love.
突き進むなら
If we are to push forward,
二人で
the two of us.
革命道中だって
Even in the middle of a revolution,
夢に熱中
we're engrossed in our dreams.
ダメダメ
No, no,
待て待て 呪いも病も抱きしめたい
wait, wait, I want to embrace even the curses and sickness.
ここらで暴れちゃっていいよね
It's fine to run wild here, isn't it?
怖くたって 唸るぜ
Even if it's scary, I'll roar!
血泥ついたって
Even if covered in blood and mud,
守りたい
I want to protect you.
革命道中だって
Even in the middle of a revolution,
君に夢中
I'm crazy about you.
暗闇染み込む世界で見つけた
I found you in a world steeped in darkness.
センチメンタルな恋
A sentimental love.
飛べ、起こせ！ 願いは事故
Fly, trigger it! Wishing for an accident.
一世一代 さあ何賭す？ 自問自答
Once in a lifetime, now what will you bet? Self-questioning.
勝つか負けるか ドローなんてないわ
To win or lose, there's no such thing as a draw.
幕開けるわ
The curtain rises.
カッチンして ラッキーマニー
Click it, lucky money,
どっちも無理 シガーシガー
neither is happening. Cigar, cigar.
引けるか否か
Whether you back down or not
自分次第だな
is entirely up to you.
余裕で！
No sweat!
振り切り
Going all out,
全betだぜ
I'm betting it all,
イェイ イェイ イェイ イェイ
yay, yay, yay, yay!
そこどけ！
Move aside!
そうこのエース
Yeah, this ace...
かっさらうのはアタシら
...is the one we're snatching away!
Stay もういい
Stay, that's enough.
勝ったなら平常心
Keep your cool if you won.
ねプレイボーイ行け
Hey playboy, beat it.
Don't get in my way
じゃあね黙って
See ya, shut it.
ワンツースリー ワンツースリー
One, two, three, one, two, three,
ワンツースリー
one, two, three,
Sit down, sit down
ワンツースリー ワンツースリー
One, two, three, one, two, three,
ワンツースリー
one, two, three.
はーもうフリーズキメてや
Sigh, just freeze already.
投げるのは噂？嘘？才能？
What are you throwing out? Rumors? Lies? Or talent?
そんな小さい尺じゃはかれない
You can't measure me with such a small scale.
でしょうそうでしょう
Right? Exactly.
セイ・グッド・バイや
Say goodbye!
あっちこっちそっちどっち？
Over there, over here, that way, which way?
Nothing, nothing 病む
Nothing, nothing, getting sick.
道なき道より
Rather than a pathless road,
闇々嫌
I hate the deep darkness.
空回りしそう
I might spin my wheels,
でもまだ止めないで
but don't stop me yet.
あのまれそう
I might get swallowed up.
声々 それぞれに
To each their own voice,
Get one's way!
アンタはここまで
You've reached your limit.
後ろだけ見とけ
Just watch my back.
カッチンして ラッキーマニー どっちも無理 シガーシガー
Click it, lucky money, neither is happening. Cigar, cigar.
引けるか否か 自分次第だな
Whether you back down or not is up to you.
余裕で！ 振り切り 全betだぜ イェイ イェイ イェイ イェイ
No sweat! Going all out, I'm betting it all, yay, yay, yay, yay!
そこどけ！ そうこのエース かっさらうのはアタシら
Move aside! Yeah, this ace is the one we're snatching away!
Stay もういい 勝ったなら平常心
Stay, that's enough. Keep your cool if you won.
ねプレイボーイ行け Don't get in my way じゃあね黙って
Hey playboy, beat it. Don't get in my way. See ya, shut it.
ワンツースリー ワンツースリー ワンツースリー Sit down, sit down
One, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, sit down, sit down.
ワンツースリー ワンツースリー ワンツースリー
One, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three,
まさかの倍々$
an unexpected double-down!
ワンツースリー ワンツースリー ワンツースリー Sit down, sit down
one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, sit down, sit down.
One, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, sit down, sit down.
特報！
[Special News]
フルアニメーションMV
[Full Animation MV]
配信後プレミア公開！
[Premiere release after the stream!]
MV公開に先駆けてー
[Prior to the MV release...]
ARE YOU READY?
ファッションビート
[Title: Fashion Beat]
痛くて 目を塞いでも
Even when I close my eyes in pain,
聞こえちゃう不安症
my anxiety still makes me hear it.
悩んでも変わらないから
Worrying won't change anything,
なんだかんだやるしかないか
so one way or another, I've just got to do it!
壊れるならいっそ直しやすいように
If I'm going to break, I'd rather do it in a way that's easy to fix.
どんな形目指せるかな
I wonder what kind of shape I should aim for.
助走なしのジャンプ 紐無しでダイブ
Jumping without a head start, diving without a safety rope.
今日のあたし褒めてあげたいじゃんか
Don't you think I should praise myself today?
息したい もっと 響きたい ねえ
I want to breathe... I want to resonate more, hey...
ねえあたし以上が見れるかも
Hey, you might see something even greater than me.
妄想止まんないや
My wild imagination just won't stop!
ファッションビート嗅いでみちゃう？
Wanna take a sniff of this fashion beat?
夢にあっそなんて吐けやしないな
I can't just brush off my dreams with a simple "whatever."
叶えるのはあたし自身か それとも誰かにお任せか
Am I the one to make it come true, or will I leave it to someone else?
ただただ自分に勝ちたい
I just want to win against myself, plain and simple.
ニューファッションビート愛を喰らう
This new fashion beat is devouring love.
負けるなんてごめんだ味がしないな
No way I'm losing, that's just tasteless.
何度でも灰になる進化 生まれ変わるバグの擬人化
An evolution that turns to ash again and again, a reincarnated personification of a bug.
まだまだ腐ってあげない そう、ない
I'm not going to rot away just yet, no, I won't.
チクチク刺してくるのは 飽き飽きしてるわ
I'm sick and tired of these constant, prickly jabs.
ごめん鬱雑い言葉遊びはどうかちゃんと仕舞っておいて
Sorry, but please put away those annoying wordplays.
あたしこそがライバル 当たり前の解釈
I am my own rival, that's the obvious truth.
どうしたらいい分かってるのに
Even though I know exactly what I should do.
助走なしのジャンプ 紐無しでダイブ
Jumping without a head start, diving without a safety rope.
今日のあたし出来る気しないなって
Even if I feel like I can't pull it off today...
気にしないなんて無理じゃない？ねえ
Is it really impossible to just ignore it? Hey...
ねえあたし以外と比べても
Even if you compare me with anyone else...
クソつまんないじゃんか
it's just so damn boring, isn't it?
ファッションビート嗅いでみちゃう？
Wanna take a sniff of this fashion beat?
夢にあっそなんて吐けやしないな
I won't just say "whatever" to my dreams
叶えるのはあたし自身か
Is it me who will make them come true...
それとも誰かにお任せか
...or will I leave it to someone else?
ただただ自分に勝ちたい
I just want to win against myself
ニューファッションビート 愛を喰らう
New Fashion Beat, devouring love
負けるなんてごめんだ 味がしないな
No way I'm losing, it's just tasteless
何度でも灰になる進化
Evolution that turns to ashes again and again
生まれ変わるバグの擬人化
The personification of a reborn bug
まだまだ腐ってあげない そう、ない
I won't rot away just yet, no I won't
止まれない
I can't stop
誰かじゃない あたし自身だ
It's not someone else, it's me
生まれ変わるバグの擬人化
The personification of a reborn bug
まだまだ散ってあげない そう、ない
I won't scatter away just yet, no I won't
みんな、ライブ見てくれてありがとう！
Thank you everyone for watching the live show!
これからは告知のお時間です！
Now, it's time for some announcements!
まずはこちら！
First up, this!
さくらみこ誕生日記念2026記念グッズです！
Sakura Miko Birthday Celebration 2026 commemorative goods!
まずは1つ目、こちら！たらん！
First of all, the first item is this! Tada!
アクリルパネル！
Acrylic Panel!
イラストレーターはおるだん先生に描き下ろしていただきました！
The illustrator is Orudan-sensei, who drew this brand new illustration!
テーマは、電脳世界のみこ！
The theme is "Miko in the Cyberworld"!
新衣装のみこを描き下ろしてもらいました！
She drew Miko in her new outfit!
オーロラ加工でキラキラのアクリルパネルとなっております！めっちゃ可愛い！
It's a sparkling acrylic panel with an aurora finish! Super cute!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
スマホスタンドフィギュアです！
Smartphone Stand Figure!
スマホが立てかけられるスタンド、そして新衣装のみこのフィギュア！
A stand where you can prop up your smartphone, and a figure of Miko in her new outfit!
めちゃくちゃ可愛くないですか？これ、細部までこだわったのでね、ぜひね
Isn't it incredibly cute? I was really particular about the details for this, so please...
あの、このスタンドにスマホを立てかけて、配信見てくれたら嬉しいです！
...prop your smartphone on this stand and watch my streams! I'd be so happy!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
ガジェットケース！
Gadget Case!
新衣装にちなんで、ちょっとこういう、あまり出さないグッズも考えてみました！
Inspired by the new outfit, I thought of a merchandise item we don't usually release!
ケーブルとかね、モバイルバッテリーなど、小物を収納できるケースとなっております！
It's a case where you can store small items like cables and mobile batteries!
ソフトな素材になっているよ！
It's made of a soft material!
最後はこちら！
Last but not least, this!
ナイロンジャケット！
Nylon Jacket!
新衣装をモチーフにしたナイロンジャケットとなっております！
This nylon jacket is themed after the new outfit!
ちょっとかっこよ目のね、デザインなので、みんな、一緒に、お揃いになってくれたら嬉しいです！
It has a slightly cooler design, so I'd love it if we could all match!
そして、フルセット購入特典はこちら！
And here is the full set purchase bonus!
さくらみこ直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入り、おるだん描き下ろしポストカードとなっております！
A postcard drawn by Orudan-sensei, featuring Sakura Miko's handwritten signature and a foil-stamped duplicated message!
こちらは数量限定にはなるんですが、みんなお早めに！よろしくお願いします！
This is limited in quantity, so make sure to get yours early! Thank you!
そして通常版は、え、さくらみこ箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入りのポストカードとなっております！
And the regular version comes with a postcard featuring Sakura Miko's foil-stamped duplicated signature and message!
みんな、あの、あの、ぜひね、たくさん手に入れてくれると嬉しいです！よろしくお願いします！
Everyone, I'd be so happy if you could get your hands on lots of them! Thank you!
そして、告知2つ目は、こちら！
And the second announcement is this!
なんと！さくらみこ×学研さんの参考書シリーズが発売決定になりました！
Unbelievable! A study reference book series in collaboration with Gakken is set to be released!
ホロライブStudyBook「さくらみこでもわかる」シリーズとなっております！
It's the Hololive Study Book "Easy Enough for Sakura Miko" series!
「中学漢字＋語彙」「中学数学」「中学英単語」「中学地理＋都道府県」の4冊が発売決定です！
Four books: "Junior High Kanji + Vocab", "Junior High Math", "Junior High English Vocab", and "Junior High Geography + Prefectures" are confirmed for release!
そして、初回限定の愛蔵版も発売予定となっております！
Also, a first-press limited collector's edition is planned for release!
4月下旬頃より予約開始なので、引き続き続報をチェックしてね！
Pre-orders start around late April, so please stay tuned for more updates!
「みこでもわかる」シリーズ、うーん、みんな説得力があると思うよね？
The "Easy Enough for Miko" series... I'm sure you all find that highly convincing, right?
次！3つ目は、こちら！
Next! The third announcement is this!
さくらみこ×フレーベル館、初の絵本「みこぴーとおおきなさくらのき」が、本日より発売です！
Sakura Miko × Froebel-kan's first picture book, "Mikopi and the Big Cherry Tree", is on sale starting today!
もう買ってくれた人もいるかな？
Maybe some of you have bought it already?
いつも支えてくれているみこぴーを題材に、夢だった絵本を作ることができました！
Based on Mikopi, who always support me, I was able to make my dream picture book a reality!
全国の書店やローソンさんで購入可能なので、ぜひぜひみんな手に取ってください！よろしくお願いします！頑張りました！
It's available at bookstores nationwide and Lawson, so please pick up a copy! Thank you! I worked really hard!
続いてはこちら、大発表！
Next up is this major announcement!
4つ目は、こちら！
The fourth announcement is this!
さくらみこ、フィギュア化が決定しました！
Sakura Miko's figure adaptation has been confirmed!
おるだん先生監修にて、みこの夢だった等身大フィギュアがついに完成です！やったー！
Supervised by Orudan-sensei, Miko's dream life-sized figure is finally complete! Yay!
スケールフィギュアも同時に予約販売が決まりました！
The scale figure will also be available for pre-order at the same time!
明日3月6日から予約開始です！
Pre-orders start tomorrow, March 6th!
エキスポのデザインココさんブースで展示されるので、みんな見に来てね！たくさん写真撮ってね！
It will be on display at the Design COCO booth at the Expo, so please come see it! Take lots of photos!
また、この等身大フィギュアも展示される、
Also, where this life-sized figure will be displayed...
京都IP書店×さくらみこのポップアップショップも開催決定となりました！すごい！
...the Kyoto IP Bookstore × Sakura Miko Pop-up Shop is also confirmed! Amazing!
リニューアルオープンした京都 蔦屋IP書店
At the newly renovated Kyoto Tsutaya IP Bookstore...
...記念で、4月28日から開催でーす！
...celebration, starting from April 28th!
オリジナルグッズの販売や、えー、ノベルティのコラボも行われるので
With original merchandise sales and novelty collaborations,
みなさん楽しみにしてください！
everyone, please look forward to it!
盛りだくさんだー！
There's so much in store!
そして！まだございます！
And that's not all!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
さくらみこ×HYTE コラボPCケース発売決定！
The Sakura Miko x HYTE collab PC case is confirmed!
キーキャップとデスクマットのセットもございます
A keycap and desk mat set is also available!
先行予約リリースのメール通知や詳細については
For early reservation email notifications and details,
hyte.co/miko を見てみてください
please check out hyte.co/miko!
楽しみに待っててね！
Please look forward to it!
そして！
And...
今年もさくらみこ×鳴門鯛焼本舗さんのコラボが実施中ですね！
...the Sakura Miko x Naruto Taiyaki Honpo collab is underway!
今年でなんと4回目です！ありがとうございます！
This is actually our fourth time! Thank you so much!
3月31日までなので、みんなぜひ食べに行ってください！
It runs until March 31st, so please go try some!
続いて！
Next up...
新曲「ファッションビート」本日0時よりリリースでーす！
My new song, "Fashion Beat", releases tonight at midnight!
MVはこのあとプレミア公開！みんな見てね！
The music video premieres right after this! Check it out!
とっても豪華なアニメMVとなっております。よろしくお願いしまーす！
It's a gorgeous animated MV! I hope you like it!
はい、そしてこちら！
All right, and next!
明日からホロライブエキスポとセブンスフェス開催でーす！
The Hololive Super Expo and 7th Fes start tomorrow!
3日間の開催ですよ！すごい！
It's a three-day event! Amazing!
えーみこはですね、セブンスフェスではDay2のステージ2に参加します
For the 7th Fes, I'll be participating in Stage 2 on Day 2!
みんな、見に来てねー！
Be sure to come watch!
このあとは、メンバー限定の撮影会もあるので、
And after this, we'll have a members-only photoshoot,
みんな、みこぴーになってね！
so join the Mikopi family!
ということで、こちらがもりもりの森になりましたが、
We had a mountain of announcements today,
みんなついてこれたかな？
but I hope you all kept up!
みここれからも頑張るので、よろしくお願いします！
I'll keep doing my best, so please support me!
誕生日祝ってくれてありがとう！おつみこー！
Thank you for celebrating my birthday! Otsumiko!
誕生日記念 2026
[Birthday Celebration 2026]
アクリルパネル
[Acrylic Panel]
スマホスタンドフィギュア
[Smartphone Stand Figure]
ガジェットケース
[Gadget Case]
ナイロンジャケット
[Nylon Jacket]
誕生日記念フルセット
[Birthday Celebration Full Set]
hololive production OFFICIAL SHOPにて販売
[Available at hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP]
生誕LIVE 2026♡ 今年も祝ってくれてありがとうじぇい！
Birthday Live 2026! Thank you for celebrating with me again this year!